Welcome to Psyche Awakens, a show in the panel verse where tarot, truth and raw conversation meet.
We explore boldly, we disagree intelligently and we protect the circle.
Here's how we roll.
House rules.
Debate ideas, not people.
No doxing, slander, hate or threats, ever.
Bring receipts, claims need sources or timestamps, no rumour relays, signal discipline, mix muted
and less called, no spam, no derail, the mods are the guardians, warning time out, ban,
no negotiations mid-show.
This is Psyche's channel, Psyche's Rules.
He keeps it safe, sharp and on topic.
Use common sense and be respectful to everyone and you will be fine.
Contribute or be entertained welcome if you're here to sow chaos hang out. There's a place for you here, too
Now welcome your host psyche. See ya storyteller and your host eat truth first shadow second
Let's get into it
I like this stage
Pour my heart out page by page
I've been steady I've been true all I want is to share with you
I open the doors I let all in
Haters friends, where do I begin?
I give the mic, I share the space
Hoping kindness will find its place
I came in the spirit of...
They call me names, they twist my face
I'm blamed for storms I didn't make
I stand my ground, I take the blows
But my heart remembers every stone
Patience wears, but I won't break
Still, there's only so much I can take
Those are my tricks.
Oh my gosh, these are bright, they're shining bright.
Hey, burning joint.
Can you see it?
I think they're pretty. Wow, when the 20 people get in here, I have a new song to premiere. Wow, it's going to be a great song too.
It's going to be called My Revenge.
Let me see. Well, it's called something else, but I'm not going to say. I'll let it explain itself.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm
I do have an Etsy store, Secky Awakens on Etsy.
You can go to my channel description.
I have some readings that are available.
If you're gonna pay, well, go ahead and pay.
The cash up is here.
If you'd like a longer reading,
if not, I'll do a free reading.
No worries.
Oops.
Hold on one second.
But I think you're probably just,
probably just a,
Troll just from them. Well, because why would you say is this no longer a terror channel like because I haven't said anything yet?
So why would you say that so obviously or troll so but anyone would is serious. There you go
You can check that out. I have a banner to the banner
20 people are gonna play a new song. Let me see
Let's see 15. Yeah, there we go
There we go, there's all the kinds of things you can do this channel
Okay
There we go, hey Sam and how are you good to see ya? Thank you. Thank you
Thank you
I have been on a lot right oh I started my own kitty gang it's called the Bates
kitty gang BKG it's stands for I don't know if there's another another BKG but
you know a lot one second fix my shit there we go there we go
It ever starts with BKG, right? I hope I hope I'm gonna get sued by the
Anybody else well Burger King might sue me because they're Burger King grill, right? I
don't know
So
You just move that
To get the 20 people I will
Premier the new song. It's not it's not the flirty diamond song. I just that was the premiere in the last episode
I do a lot of premieres
I'm actually really proud of
Hey, what's up money for 20?
Yeah, the baits kitty gang, that's it
BKG everybody baits kitty gang when I join I'm the gang leader
Yeah, I don't think there's another oh
Thank you. Okay
We have a we have a reading
Shit hold on one second. Okay. I see okay. Yeah, but we have a we have a reading. Thank you so much
Hey, okay, the lurker. Thank you
You got a reading. I'll give you a nice long reading
For the lurker
Thank you for thank you so much for purchasing a reading and I really appreciate you. Thank you
Awesome. Thank you so much
Okay, let's see what we got. Thank you
Okay, I'll do at least 10 cards for you maybe a little more maybe I'll get a couple decks out to another one
Okay, this is what it's about guys.
Okay, so we have eight of swords.
Okay, so in the past,
you've been trapped in your own mind about something.
Now this is all mental.
You know, it's a feeling something.
And so, you know, your mind is very powerful.
So if you feel like you're trapped in your mind,
you're not necessarily really trapped,
but you're stuck in your head about something
or you have been, okay?
I think you've been getting out of this, but.
Yeah, so that's the Eight of Swords. It's kind of famous card for
mental and mental entrapment, okay?
You've been feeling restricted in the past, okay? Maybe abandoned, okay?
But you've been moving away from this because we have
Let's see. This is the Six of Swords. So moving out moving away from it going on to calmer waters, okay?
and freeing yourself from this mental entrapment, okay?
We have a lot of mental energy going on
with all these swords coming out so far.
Okay, so we have the moon card.
The moon card is there's something still hidden
to be revealed for you, okay?
And this will be revealed just like the moon
goes through different phases.
You know, the illusions will eventually shatter
and you will be, you know, everything will be revealed
in its own time.
You also have this queen of wands. I don't know if there's a woman in your life
This really strong courageous confident woman. This is a good woman. You know, it is
Mrs. Bates, right? There's Mrs. Bates right there
Norman Bates's mother
But I think this okay. Yep. Okay, so this woman is also very determined and will be a great and passionate inspiration for you
Okay
Okay, now we have the Nine of Swords, okay.
The Nine of Swords is feeling a lot of some kind of anxiety,
something keeping you awake at night, okay.
Boy, we're getting a lot of swords in this reading,
so there's a lot, your mental activity
is going really, really strong right now.
But, you know, don't let the,
these are all basically illusions.
You know, they could be kind of maybe nightmares
or maybe something keeping you awake, but.
I would say practice some kind of deep breathing meditation, okay?
Also the higher fend. You're being called onto some higher path, maybe a traditional path.
And also this this higher fend can see through the veil. Also things will be revealed to you, okay?
This one says he sees through the material world into your very soul, okay?
It's a connection with God also. It's also being called on to a higher path
We also have this this is a six of wands. This is a victory
But this says victory at what cost, okay? So you make sure that you know, it's worth it for you. Okay?
You got the burning joint kitty kitty gang. Okay, we're gonna start a whole a whole bunch of kitty gangs, okay?
Yeah, so six of wands is a victory though
I think you're gonna be able to power through any of this anxiety you're having
You know again, it's all in your head. Oh
Okay, we have the king of pentacles. This is you know cutting through that and coming into some abundance
It says the man who has everything, okay?
It also could be somebody you meet or somebody that wants to invest in you, but definitely
some kind of material abundance ahead, okay?
Ooh, these two came out together.
We have the four of cups.
The four of cups is like maybe bored with what you have,
the things you have,
and there's like another cup being handed to you.
You're gonna want to like turn your head
and be receptive to taking this new cup,
because this cup is what you've been waiting for.
Maybe like the first four were like,
or the first three were,
Or like a not something that satisfied you, but this one will okay, so just keep it sometimes instead of three times the charm four times
The charm, okay, and this came out with this
Four of swords, okay, and so this is also coming out of this anxiety. Wow
You've been experiencing a lot of anxiety. Okay, you really I do recommend
Some kind of meditation something to center yourself
because I see all this mental activity there's just like so many swords here which has to do
with mental activity okay okay you also have this ace of cups this is that but in those four
cups this is this ace is what is being handed to you okay out of those four so this is this is that
this is that right there this is something that can grow into something that will make you really
Hand of God. Okay. Also justice. You will be receiving justice for something. This could be some kind of
legal case or it could just be some kind of
karmic thing balance in your life
Things we've made fair for you. Okay, I'm gonna pull three more out of this deck
I'll get you another card out of the project. So just stay balanced this temperance card to stay balanced
You know, take the good with the bad. You can also do some alchemy. You can turn a negative into a positive. Okay
Said three more out of this deck, right? Okay. Okay, let's see. We have this ace of pentacles
Also something being handed to you that can grow it materially. You've got a couple aces up your sleeve
Okay, and so this ace of pentacles. It's like a seed
It'll grow into abundance. Okay
And I'll do one more from this deck for you ooh the star, okay?
Eventually, okay, so this is like a very very positive card. This is like overflowing happiness overflowing also some star power
You got this this sun behind you
Everything will work out. Everything will work out. Okay, also would make a wish upon a star
I would say for that. Okay, let me grab another deck for you
Cuz I'm gonna make sure you have a nice reading because I do really do appreciate you and thank you for
Allowing me to showcase my tarot
Okay, so where's my animal card, and I'll grab this deck, which I rarely use, but I got a couple more for you.
Here's an animal spirit deck for you.
What animal spirit am I picking up for you?
Okay, you got, ooh, the Jaguar.
You got the Jaguar, okay?
I don't know if you'd like have a connection to cats
or big cats, this is wholeness, divinity, and rebirth.
Native American tribes of North, South, and Central America
consider the Jaguar, especially its black panther form
to wield powerful magic.
Shamans would invoke Jaguar power to heal diseases
or exactly revenge on an enemy.
The cross and a circle design of this painting
Represented divinity or eternity in many civilizations, the depiction of jaguars among the Mayan and Olmec civilizations of Highland, Mexico,
often incorporated across frame by a cartouche. This iconographic device was a symbol of sky, heaven and divinity.
The painting also shows a white human face appearing below the black jaguar,
which suggests a polarity, a tension of opposites within the framed hole.
Olmec art forms often show two jaguars together,
suggesting a similar polarity or dual nature.
At times, the jaguar was shown engaged in intercourse with a human,
a reference to the mythical origins of the jaguar people.
Okay? Oh, your people? Yes.
Okay, great. Great.
And, let me get, this is a deck called Cartes de Visite.
These are just basically a fun little deck.
And you can take from it what you will,
cause these are a little bit of eccentric fun cards.
And I just wanna pull one for you.
Okay.
This says Professor Von Skellit inspires a class with another useful lesson. Are you some kind of teacher inspiring people?
I think you're a good teacher of something. Okay, and so
I would say I
would say I'm sharing knowledge and teaching somebody something
It says University of Berlin, 1888.
I don't know, but you might want to examine
how you're teaching.
I think you're able to teach and inspire, okay?
So that's your reading.
I do hope you enjoyed that, and thank you so much.
Okay, there you go.
Okay, we've got 19 people here.
I'm about to share the new song.
Let me just put these cards down.
Okay, that was a pleasure.
And thank you.
You're very welcome, you're very welcome.
I hope you enjoyed that at any time.
So thank you, thank you.
Okay, we're almost at 20 people,
then I can premiere the new song.
And I hope you guys will enjoy this.
Let's see, it should be any minute,
maybe 19 people's fine to start it at.
You can just premiere it.
Here's a new song guys. Hope you enjoy.
He said nah, now he's losing the fight
Typing in the shadows, throwing shade and
Cuts like foam, you live rent free in a house not your own
Docks don't like it's warfare but it's just that play
Well, Psyche's got an empire streaming away
You wanted his love but you couldn't command
Now you're stuck empty with junk in your hands
The world keeps on turning
When the night's trying so hard, but you can't
That's one of my favorite songs from now on.
Wow, that song is great.
That was the best.
Oh no, Rodimus Prime is back.
Oh no, that wasn't good.
I think it was great.
Yeah, it wasn't good.
It was great, actually.
It was fabulous, fabulous.
Okay.
Anyhow.
Go Wilds, give it.
Da-da-da-da-da. It was awful. Oh, you're awful. Hey, Mod. Can you kick out that uh, sacrifice that person to the abyss, please?
Please please please
Okay
Okay guys, I was awful. Hmm. Well, you're awful. You're awful. I
Loved it. I loved it
personally I loved it just hit all the right notes hit all the right notes
oh bye sacrifice to Cthulhu gone forever oh I I wouldn't want to kiss the
disgusting hairy thing no thank you I have better taste
I think I'm gonna I want to play the other version of it. Let me see that was that one
Like there's a couple versions to each of them, so let's try the other one
Let's do that. How about that?
Let's see
How about this guys try this one
The same one it's the same one. Okay, hold on. I got it. I got it
This one
Sweetest revenge
basement chewing on regret got a keyboard on me but no paycheck yet sending
pizza scrap man manure at the door psyche just laughs can't hurt him anymore
he came out one night the love would ignite psyche said nah now he's losing
the fight typing in the shadows throwing shade in disguise
That was good! So much better. Oh god, I loved writing that song.
That is great. So how's everyone doing today? Good to see you.
You're welcome. Hey Samantha. Hey everybody.
Hey Burning Joint, Nick. What's up?
Sam and what's up, dude dude ski
Link, okay, you got it. I'll pin it to hold on. There's the link
Got mr. Arthur come on up Arthur
Thank you, Paul. Thank you
That was a good song
You know I
Have a I have ways of fighting back to
Hey, Arthur
Yo, I
Can't hear you
Boom, yo, I hear you now
Yeah, you're breaking up a little bit. What's up? Oh shit. You're good. You're good. No good good
Request sure
Could you possibly do that salsa song but not include the tranny? Can you do it just like just for you?
You know no tranny in there. Well, that's because flirty diamond was on last night with auto and auto is like a
He's a straight man. He's a straight. He's Hispanic
He lives in a Canada and he actually said like he's wanting to bend over for flirty diamond last night and so
You know, it was kind of an epic love story. So
Yeah
You could do that for me. Okay. Well, I'll make an Arthur song
Let's do it. Yeah. Yeah, definitely the salsa version. That'd be awesome. You want to salsa song? Okay. Yeah, I appreciate that
I'll make you a song and we'll just take a little bit
But it all I have to write it and then put it to music and stuff. So
By today by tonight, I'll have a song for you. Okay, and I'll premiere it when you when you come in
Be an Arthur song
Okay
You got it. You've got it. Oh, there you go
You got it for you. You're doing amazing work with the AI man. I wish I knew how you're doing it. I'd love to
Thank you. Well, you know, if you'd like to schedule
Schedule some time with me. I will be happy to walk you through everything and that's if that goes for anybody
I will do I can do training because it is all about the prompting
That's and there's like a few few little secrets to it. That's why I'm able to do it so well, so
Um, but I love uh, you got it, dude. I love uh, yeah, I love people with one word shampoo. Well, but my hair's
Oh my gosh. Oh, we'll KC
But oh, is it KZ? Oh, come on. Thank you, brother. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you psych
Love you. Thank you. Love you too, brother
You have a great day. You too, man. Okay. Thank you
Anytime anytime. Arthur's a good friend. Hey, joney
Yes, whenever you like, in private or on the show,
whenever you like, Joni, you got it.
I'm happy to help you.
Good to see you.
Yeah, and I do apologize for the other night.
I know some inappropriate stuff was said on the show,
and I was kind of like, what was I doing at the time?
I was not focused on the show, so I do apologize.
I love you, Joni.
Um, yeah, how are you guys doing? I'm gonna let's pull a card out of this this deck right here
This is for everybody. This is a great deck
This one says
Sweet little addy a dainty lass full of it says poison charm
But it changes it to poison and harm and look at cute little there's cute little addy
You know, yeah
I know these cards are you know, they're pretty unique. I
It's kind of like a it's called the cabinet curiosities. It's the carte de visite
20 disturbing cabinet cards. This is by the deviant move company
I don't think she would be, I don't think she would say that,
hey, Barry, hey, Barry, no problem.
It was, it was fun.
And I want to thank you for buying that reading.
You know, it wasn't necessarily a receptive audience.
You know, but that's the test of a good reader is like,
even, am I able to do an honest, good reading
despite all the stuff going on in the background?
And I thought I'd tried to.
And then the one card that they were saying,
I didn't know what it meant.
I said exactly what it meant.
Even said the exact words right on the card. So I don't know what what that was about, but thank you
And you know Kate wasn't too harsh on me. I
Don't know who that woman was that her name was Shannon or Sharon or something like that, but um, she was a rude
rude person
But and I don't think Alex would suggest that but Alex
It's a huge, huge, huge supporter and a help of mine.
And, you know, I love her and she can say whatever she wants
because I will owe the Shannon from Generic Gen X.
Yeah, she was pretty rude.
She was pretty rude.
So you're hungry?
Well, look what I got.
Look what I got.
Don't get jealous, but look what I got.
If you're hungry, this is a good thing to eat.
Oh my gosh, my nails, I'm sorry.
I'm hungry, I'm eating a good delicious avocado toast, so.
I think guys are doing good today.
Hoo, it's a little bit hot in Los Angeles.
Yeah, I'm gonna hop in the shower soon, or the bath.
I'd like to take baths, how about you guys?
Do you like baths or showers?
So if you missed it, I do have the Flirty Diamond Auto Song.
I like the second part, yeah, I like this one better.
In the glow of neon, she's caught in the night
A blade in her hand, a fire in her eyes so bright
He shows up in red, with a hose and...
Like a secret sharp as a knife, but maybe she's tired of the dangers
Life he drops his shirt with a volunteer's pride
She's smirking but softening somewhere inside
Where the story began, from blades to badges, from sparks to trust, could true...
Okay, let me respond to this
Kate
Yeah, I got you BC. Oh, really? Okay. Sure Kate. I have no problem with I'm actually a member of Kate's chat
And so it's funny if she's harassing her own members. I haven't seen too many members either. So, you know, I'm actually a member and
You know
She wants to hire people I am her probably her biggest competition because on my YouTube it says like your competitors
It says beep beep and Kate they come up
So, you know, I understand but I don't consider her competition. She has her own kind of show
I have my own kind of show and so did you okay? I got you beat big thick
Seven of cups. Okay, so would they come okay seven of cups so seven of cups is like a little bit of a confusion card
Okay, so in the past, or in the recent past,
you may have been presented with a lot of options
and I'm a little confused about which way to go.
I would say maybe go towards the one
that's most appealing towards you
because there's a lot of good options,
but some of them are whammy's, you know?
Also, we got this ace of swords.
This is a truth, okay?
You got the truth coming, or you know the truth.
And so that may be helping you make a decision,
the right decision, this is sort of truth, right?
We also have the Nine of Pentacles and Nine of Pentacles is about abundance. It's about being surrounded by good things able to manifest
It's you know an earth card
and so I think that you're really enjoying your surroundings and you know, what's around you and
Able to I see like birds birds coming to your finger and stuff like that
Just in in sync in harmony in sync with the earth
We're the fortune things are gonna be going into your favor
Okay, luck is in your side that the Wheel of Fortune is on your side. You've got the
It's like it says pick a fate any fate, you know
of course, you know what we all have a
fate as a human being but
Also, we have the Hierophant for you. You want a dog rescue? Awesome. That is beautiful. I love people working with animals
You also have the Hierophant. It's also like maybe like looking into this this higher path of traditional path
This is also about being able to see beyond the veil because it says he sees through the material world into your very soul
Okay, I think you probably have that ability. I'm gonna pull one more word of advice for you
Okay, nine of cups. This says, you know
Some relaxation, you know, I think you work really hard and it's like just make time to pamper yourself
Enjoy enjoy your life and to relax. Okay. Take a nice warm bath
Relax meditate that kind of thing. So I hope you like that
It's your reading
Yeah, did your dick pick expire?
Know yours. Oh, yeah, cuz you're not a mod. Okay. Well
It did.
You have to send me a new one, Barry,
but I got you, Barry,
because you're a good friend of mine.
There you go, Barry.
You know, Barry is,
he's not always been perfectly nice to me,
but I do appreciate.
He once tried to mod me in a,
oh, you're very welcome, you're very welcome.
He once tried to mod me in Kate's chat
He's like, no, Psyche can't be a mod here.
But he tried, so I appreciate that.
You're welcome, Barry, you're welcome.
Just to have my back if you can, if you can.
Not like I'm like, I like my mods to if they're not,
you know, at least defending me, at least not,
they're not slandering me, OK?
So there you go, Barry.
Yeah, Barry's a good guy.
Very funny too. A lot funnier than the Eldo character. Eldo is lame
You know, there's something even Vita like there's somebody named HIV awakens tarot. Oh, you got my back too big
Okay, hold on. I'll mod you
Yeah
What was I gonna say? Oh, yeah, Bita in her chat
There's somebody named HIV awakens tarot and beat is like change your name and then elder was like no no no no
Don't have him change his name. That's good. It's it's fine. It's fine. It's fine like
I mean and beat is not the biggest fan of mine right now, but even she's like that's a little bit like you know
a bit of a disgusting username to have.
So I don't know why Eldo is so eager
to have me slandered with HIV
and know I don't have HIV or anything like that.
I don't know if I need to do a bloodstream on air.
You've been watching Kate Streams a lot back then,
she would say, let's go harass Psyche.
Well, you know what?
I like to convert my haters
into either motivators or my fans, you know?
And so,
Oh, and by the way the people that are coming for scrap metal those are some really nice people like everybody
I've talked to because I sometimes I would just let them knock and stuff like that
But I went downstairs last time and told them they're really nice people and they're like oh my and they can't believe that they got
You know hoodwinked by this idiot, you know putting a fake ad out
Trying to bother people. I mean, it's like but they're at least maybe I'll make some new friends and stuff like that, you know
Ha ha, thank you. Thank you, Vic
Oh, you got my back auto has my front what I like Paul so I hear to your guys. Let's go harass psyche
She's about to end her live streams. Okay. Well, you know what even if she says go harass them
That's brings people to my chat, right? And I could just
Hide them and stuff, you know
It's it's not a big deal. It's you know, there's especially with the gay community. We have a saying
It's like any publicity is good publicity because we've been like so so slandered like it because basically in every horror movie
They'd have like a transgender or a gay
Serial killer like Norman Bates was a cross-dresser. They had a movie called
Cruisers I think about like, you know, this guy that would pick up gay
Hustlers and like, you know murder them and stuff. They silenced the lambs Buffalo Bill
Tony are you're not Tony? You're not the bad Tony, right?
you're bringing hell with me watch your channel grow yeah bring yeah come on you know
guys you know i'm i've had trolls around i'm used to dealing with trolls i know how to troll back
and so let me just okay okay with tony lives in los angeles like us oh oh yeah that's paul i know paul
paul's a good guy i'm gonna mod paul hold on paul's in my city let me see paul
Yeah, I got a lot of mods now four minutes till 420. Yeah, let's smoke it up
Also, there's been people saying oh, well this person's a managing modest. I don't have any managing mods except for
Jamie and nightbot are my managing mods, you know, Jamie's been with me forever
So I know I don't have like, you know, everybody has a managing mod. I just have like, you know
Basically just Jamie so you're from the IE. Oh awesome
Yeah
so
This is Paul Paul is a really cool guy. He's a really he's a really sweet guy
So here's here's my new song if you haven't heard it yet. This is a great song
Yeah, there's a bad one, but this is the background right here
Tony's in the basement chewing on regret got a keyboard on me, but no paycheck yet sending pizza scrap men
Manure at the door, but Psyche just laughs, can't hurt him anymore
He came out one night, thought love would ignite
Psyche said nah, now he's losing the fight
Typing in the shadows, throwing shade in disguise
But everyone can see the b-
Defensitas, rap metal people, um,
they're asking me on shows.
Hey, round them up and talk to me some music.
Y ahora todo va a ser un viejo...
Okay, if your friend Dominic. Yeah, get him up here. Yeah. Hey, Kate
And I hope it's the real Kate cuz I went to the channel and it's like, you know, two videos
So I don't know if it's you but hopefully it is you could come up and verify it with me
Just so I know for sure, but I have no problem with you Kate
You know, I don't consider you an enemy
You're kind to me when I'm on your show. You're respectful. You didn't you weren't like piling on like everybody else was
You had me up. You let me do a reading
You know I have no problem
So
And I think you're, I think you're pretty funny, actually.
That's like, from the first time,
even when you did that show about me that says,
oh, Psyche, the weirdo lurker.
And you could have been harder on me and you weren't like,
you know, you know how people are with me sometimes.
Like they're pretty harsh.
And you're basically just funny.
So I think you're one of the good trolls.
And I respect you as a panel versus host.
I try to respect all the panel versus people
because we're colleagues, basically.
I'm going to put a few of these songs up. Let me see. I'm going to publish.
Yeah, I have some new shorts coming out. There we go, guys. I hope that these are good.
I don't really censor my shorts. Let me see. Okay, there's a prophecy. Okay,
There we go, I'm publishing some new shorts discover the exciting features of the psyche verse, which is this one
Okay, yeah, the psyche verse is up
I'll even put Kate in the psyche verse if she wants to
It'll take a little time. I'm still in the middle in the sock puppet troll cautionary tail. Perfect. I got some good shorts up right there, okay?
Whoo, it's a little bit warm today
Okay
So let's see
Well, I don't really know I
Think I've done all the talking on the show like I've talked a lot like I know people are like shut up
So if anyone wants to come up or you like follow boy, I think it kind of sounds like who do I like?
What's the one?
Falling in reverse. Does anyone know that band? I like falling in reverse
Yeah, so but that's why I'm like if I have to babysit. I just basically I
Don't I just you know, I let people be who they are or I'd block them if they're just too too bad
But I don't mind funny troll, but they're getting much more rare, right?
But I know yeah, so but I really do like
Making songs and stuff. Hi guys. Wow a nice 30 people in chat. I don't know. So I don't know
Maybe I can show you some of what happened last night with the flirty and
Flirty and auto let me just do a little quick little replay just the last time I'm not trying to do a rerun or something like that
I'm just gonna do a quick
quick
Recap of what happened last night, so that was let me see that was return of flurry diamond in auto
I fell asleep during it
Watch this
Oh
I'll see who's worth you. I'll
All right
You know what I mean? She got
I don't I don't I like
Here we go. Here we go.
Wait, let me hear this.
What the fuck?
What do you say? Oh my god.
That's what you said.
You know when you come up when you can get my live reaction what I don't want I don't want you getting mad
But why why you did that to me girl? Why the reason you did cuz I got it. It's all about finessing
Wow, that's crazy
That's all you gotta get that money on but you didn't you didn't know
I don't care
Dollars I needed a hundred
Wow
Gotta get that finesse up, you know
Kisses I don't go that way. Sorry
Well
She has balls
Yeah, I don't I don't I don't I don't do those maybe you like that shit. I don't I
Don't mind having a conversation. I don't mind. I don't mind having a conversation with a person, but
You like chicks with dicks. That's all new bro. She's trans. I don't go
I am just out here my amy. She's just she's just she's just a human person
She's just human to daddy. You know, I mean, I just talked to a human person. I mean, I don't go fuck who I talk to but
You know what I mean? She got a dick. I don't I don't I like persons who got dicks
You like it. You like it. Yeah, you like it. Yeah, I understand. Yeah, I know you like it
Yeah, I understand that you might like it dry in your mouth, too
I mean
That's crazy
My god
Ok.
Dry dogs?
She's gonna do me or I'm gonna do her?
What?
Oh, you little fucking ass.
You little fucking ass.
Wait, let me hear this.
What the fuck?
That's what you said. You said you won't let her fuck you. You said you won't let buddy diamond fuck you in your ass
And then you won't fuck her in the ass, too. Damn. You're crazy, Brody
Yo
You're trying to do a switch you're trying to do a switcheroo need
I don't know if you'll be able to walk after like I am my turn I don't know if you'll be able to walk and be able to like accomplish
I'm poor, I'm poor, but I got six inches.
Oh, that's cute.
That's really cute.
Oh, shit.
I think that there's, I think that small presents are cute for certain people, but some people
I don't like, I deserve the world, you know, I deserve the world to like, I like to be
What the fuck?
Somebody said, damn, she's hot.
I respect my honey.
Yeah, this is auto, I'm very flattered, but like, I have needs.
Yo, yo, yo.
Buddy diamond.
What I don't see your
Let me down be your fuck out old drag dogs. I
Know I wouldn't be able to satisfy me in bed
You're just don't you're doing doggy star right?
I'll put on a
You have really nice teeth auto
I don't I don't I don't all you want to suck the bone dry dogs?
You want to suck the bone dry dogs?
Uh
I
Think I think I think she's sexy
I think she's my master you
Answer my question you all you want to suck that bone dry dogs. Oh my god. This is well
Maybe. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh
Yes, oh, yeah, I missed the conversation. I just need everybody in chat was like no she gave her like $600
I was like no Miguel gave Dom and no money
But this is hilarious, I'm gonna mute up and let you do your thing girl. I'm watching
Because auto doesn't even have cash trap so it's like
I don't are you gonna let it you know cash ever
You don't got cash up. You don't have PayPal, Novel, Benimo.
Summer. Summer. Summer. Summer. I'm poor. I ain't got a dollar.
But, but you want some dick, that's for sure.
Oh, I'm like, when I was eight inches, I was eight inches now.
That one's got a big dick, so you better bend over, buddy.
He doesn't even want to, like, he doesn't want to start off with a little bit.
He wants to, like, just go big, you know, just go bigger.
Honestly, Summer, I want something, I want something.
Oh, yeah, I know you want that dick you didn't even see
Little like very clear what you want. We know you want that dick
You show us your condoms and everything you're ready
You're ready you're ready for that dick because like I
I'm ready. I'm ready. I don't know if you're really, are you really ready for that?
Looking, looking like you, looking like you're looking. I think you're very cute. I'm ready.
Yeah. I'm ready. Yeah, I'm ready. Have you ever took dick before, Otto?
I have never took a dick before. So you're going to, your diamond will be your first.
Wow
You know
Like he'll be like raging now like he gets fucked by a tranny and then I mean a trans am and then he ends up just turning gay fully
It's just gonna turn out like raging
He's ready
Although are you gonna end up being gay like how you ever been in prison? Have you like I'm trying to find out your story
I, I can tell you, I can tell you, I can tell you this much, okay?
I can tell you this much.
It's the other yes or no question.
I want it.
I don't think you can lock that.
We know you want to dig.
There's no doubt about that.
Yeah, we know you want to dig, but like, have you been locked up before?
Like.
Never been locked up, never been in prison.
So you're just going, you're just like, you're just thinking yourself, fuck it, I'm just going to take like some, some trans and it, wow.
Yeah, what made you want Dickton? I mean, like, what, I mean, just, I'll say, I'll say, you know, no, no King Shane. Yeah, she's got a big dick.
I'm not even eight inches. I'm really like, literally 12 inches.
I'm just like, I'm really surprised, like I'm really 12 inches.
Honestly summer. I don't even I'm not even thinking about sausage. I'm just
Oh, but you have to she was a 12-inch dick you ain't got no choice. You're gonna be takin' problems.
Okay, that was enough, but yeah guys, you can watch that back. It is called the return of auto and flirty diamond or flirty diamond and auto or something
Unfortunately, I'm getting privacy complaints. So I'm gonna have to end the stream and delete this, but yeah, I'm having fun with you guys
I'll be back later. Okay. I
Just want to say thank you for being here. I love you guys
Um, I hope you like that that was hilarious. It was fun, huh?
I love I love fun shows like that and that was you know, Flurry Diamonds been gone for a while
But some wild German lady appears. How are you?
Yeah, I um, you know, I played the new song I guess
Maybe I gave a little bit too much information away. I don't know. Well, maybe he better think about that next time
He's trying to send scrap metal people to my house to wake me up at all hours of the day
And pizzas and manure to my house, you know
Maybe you better think about that. Okay?
Think about that. Okay, I got your name. I got your number
Love you guys
I'll be back. Okay. They docks. They slander. They gaslight. They disrupt
But what if you had the ultimate guide to shut them down?
Introducing Trollopedia your field manual to decode expose and outsmart internet trolls
From classic tactics like love bombing to modern swarm attacks
Trollopedia breaks it all down. Know the playbook flip the script. Take back your power
Trollopedia